<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>ZoneInspectData [A18]</name>
	<author>Varisha</author>
	<targetVersion>0.18.1712</targetVersion>
	<url>https://ludeon.com/forums/index.php?topic=36614</url>
	<description>
Current Version: 1.1.18.2

This mod will put some basic information into the inspect window for the current selected zone. 

For zones to store things:
The mod analyzes the stored items in a zone and performs some magic. It adds a scrollable list of entries into the inspect window if a zone is selected. The default handling for other selections is not touched! The list contains an icon, the label and the total number of things in the zone. 


Single selection of farm zones:
Adds a graph to the inspect window showing the distribution of growth values of the plants in the zone.
The graph contains these information:
 - x axis = growth value in percent (a plant has growth value of 0-100%)
 - y axis = percentage of total planted plants in the zone that reached growth value x (let's say i have like 8 percent of plants that reached growth value ~52% and 13% are around 100% growth value)
 - The white vertical line marks the growth value that is needed to harvest a plant.

Below the graph you find the following information from left to right
 - Total of cells with no plant in it (this includes cells that are marked as growing zone, but have a lamp on it or so)
 - Total cells with plants in it (any growth value)
 - Total number of plants that cannot be harvested yet (left of white line)
 - Total number of plants that can be harvested (right of white line)
 - Total number of fully grown plants (growth value = 100%)

Multiple selection of farm zones:
 - List can be sorted by fully grown plants or harvestable plants (descending only)
 - Single entry in list can be selected which results in single selection view of this zone.
 
Release-Notes:
**************
v1.1.18.2:
 - farm zones single selection: Included total number of fully grown plants and realigned information below graph. You can now select the things via the icons below the graph (for harvestable and fully grown plants)
 - farm zones multiple selection: Added data view. 
 
Release-Notes:
**************
v1.1.18.1:
 - fixed graph implementation for A18 (not compatible with A17)

v1.1.17.4:
 - included graph for single selection of farm zones (not compatible with A18) 
 
v1.1.17.3
 - lists for storage zones are now sorted
 - included previously excluded entries with no icon (added at the end of the list)
	</description>
</ModMetaData>